Guide to the Stanford University, Planning Office, Records SC0486
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2005-116
  - Education Building Renovations Funded Projects (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Education Building Renovations Funded Projects (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Track House Lot Funded Project (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Driving Range Parking Funded Project (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Museum Way Parking Funded Project (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Meyer Buck Estate 1.1 General (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Meyer Buck Estate 2.1 General 2.0 Project information (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Meyer Buck Estate 3.1 General 3.0 Final report (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - GSB - Building 350 Renovation 1.1 General 1.0 Planning and programming (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - GSB - Building 350 Renovation 1.1 General 1.0 Planning and programming (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - GSB - Building 350 Renovation 3.1 General 3.0 Construction and occupancy (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - GSB - Building 350 Renovation 2.1 General 2.0 Design and documentation (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - GSB - Building 350 Renovation 4.1 General 4.0 Graphics and materials (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Aquatics Complex Funded Project (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Aquatics Complex Funded Project (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Aquatics Complex [unlabeled folder] (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 1.1 General - 1.0 Planning & Programming - (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 1.2 Background, Expectations, Formulation - 1.0 Planning & Programming - (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 1.3 Sudies and Approval - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 1.4 Environmental Issues - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 1.5 Budget and Finances - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 2.1 General - 2.0 Design & Documentation - (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 2.2 Correspondence - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 2.3 Meetings - 2.0 Design & Documentation - (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 2.4 Plans - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 3.2 New Construction - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 4.1 General - 4.0 Graphics & Materials (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Facilities Master - 4.2 Drawings and Photographs - 4.0 Graphics & Materials (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Center - 1.1 General - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Center - 1.1 Expectations - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Center - 1.2 Communication/Comments - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Center - 1.3 Meeting Notes - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Center - 2.1 Schedule - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Center - Development / Alumni Project Formulation 9-VDG-207 - (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Center - 2.1 Schedule - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Center - 2.2 Budget - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Center - 2.3 Drafts - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Center - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Center - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Center - 4.1 Renderings - 4.0 Graphics & Materials (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Center - 4.1 Renderings - 4.0 Graphics & Materials (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Alumni Center - 4.2 Landscape Plans - 4.0 Graphics & Materials (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Maloney Soccer (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Vaden Student Health Center (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Vaden Student Health Center (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Vaden Student Health Center (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Redwood City Boat House (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Redwood City Boat House - Boathouse Facility (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Parking Structure V - 1.1 General - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Parking Structure V - 1.2 Background - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Parking Structure V - 1.3 Studies/Environmental Issues - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Parking Structure V - 1.4 Feasibility Report/Approval - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Parking Structure V - 1.5 Budget/Finances - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Parking Structure V - 2.1 General - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Parking Structure V - 2.2 Guidelines - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Parking Structure V - 2.3 Correspondence - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Parking Structure V - 2.4 Consultants - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Parking Structure V - 2.5 Meetings - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Parking Structure V - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Parking Structure V - 4.1 General - 4.0 Graphics and Materials (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Parking Structure V - 4.2 Drafts and Plans - 4.0 Graphics and Materials (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Parking Structure V - 4.3 Renderings - 4.0 Graphics and Materials (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Learning Lab (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Learning Lab (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Geology Corner: file contents and Historic Structures Report - (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Geology Corner - 1.1 General - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Geology Corner - 2.1 General - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Geology Corner - 2.2 FEMA/Section 106 - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Geology Corner - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Geology Corner - 3.2 Construction Meeting Minutes - 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Geology Corner - 4.1 General - 4.0 Graphics and Materials (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Language Corner - 1.1 General - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Language Corner - 2.1 General - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Language Corner - 2.2 FEMA/Section 106 - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Language Corner - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Language Corner - 4.1 General - 4.0 Graphics and Materials (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Language Corner - 3.2 Construction Meeting Minutes - 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 18, Folder 285)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 1.1 General - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 1.2 Chronology - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 1.3 Feasibility Study Reports - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 1.4 Program Documents - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 1.5 Other Universities - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 2.2 Minutes - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 2.1 General - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 2.3 Door Survey - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 3.2 Construction Minutes - 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 4.1 General - 4.0 Graphics and Materials (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 5.1 FEMA correspondence - 5.0 FEMA/Section 106 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 5.2 Section 106 Submission - 5.0 FEMA/SEction 106 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 5.2 Section 106 Submission - 5.0 FEMA/SEction 106 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 5.5 Section 106 Historic Preservation - 5.0 FEMA/Section 106 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 5.6 MOA - 5.0 FEMA/Section 106 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 5.4 Section 106 Review: Issues of Concern - 5.0 FEMA/Section 106 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Green Library Reconstruction - 5.3 Section 106 Consultation Mth (5/93) - 5.0 FEMA/Section 106 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Lagunita Court Pre-Program - H&DS Pre-program Recommendations (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Lagunita Court Renovation - 1.1 General - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lagunita Court Renovation - CB - (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Lagunita Court Renovation - Lagunita Scope Considerations (spiral bound volume) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Lagunita Court Renovation - 2.1 General - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Lagunita Court Renovation - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction & Occuupancy (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Lagunita Court Renovation - 4.1 General - 4.0 Graphics & Materials (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Cowell Clusters (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Cowell Clusters (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Lake Houses (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lake Houses (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lake Houses (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Mirrielees (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - EV Phase II - 1.1 General - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - EV Phase II - 1.2 Cost Estimates and Budget Plans - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - EV Phase II - 1.3 Studies and Reports - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - EV Phase II - 1.4 Correspondence - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - EV Phase II - 2.1 General - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - EV Phase II - 2.2 Drafts, Drawings, and Renderings - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - EV Phase II - 2.3 Schematic Design - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - EV Phase II - 2.4 Site Plan - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - EV Phase II - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - EV Phase II - 3.2 Communication - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - EV Phase II - 3.3 Site Approval - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - EV Phase II - 3.4 Program Statement - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - EV Phase II - 4.2 Articles - 4.0 Graphics & Materials (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - EV Phase II - 5.1 All Meetings - 5.0 Meeting Minutes (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Mirrielees Phase 2 - 1.1 General - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Mirrielees Phase 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Keck Science Building (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Haas Center (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - DAPER - Sunken Diamond Parking (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Serra Mall 2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Serra Mall 2 (continued) (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Serra Mall 3 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Serra Mall 3 (continued) (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Haus Mitteleuropa (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - HEPL II (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - HEPL Office Building (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Housing Maintenance Facility (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - H&DS Maintenance Building (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - H&FS Maintenance Op. Center (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Human Anatomy Teaching Facility (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Frost Amphitheater, 1982-83 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Golf Maintenance Facility - DMP (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - GPI Projects (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Grove Mayfield (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Forsythe Computer Renovations (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Ford Quad (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Ford Quad (continued) (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Food Research Expansion (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - ESF/HVAC (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Economics/CEPR Building (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Economics/CEPR Building (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Economics/CEPR Building (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Economics/CEPR Building (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Earthquake Trailers (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - DAPER - Arrillaga Family Sports Center (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - AEL Building (Applied Electronics Lab) (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Bolivar House (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Cooksey House, 1-2 (inc. Rehab and Dev.) (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Cooksey House, 1-2 (inc. Rehab and Dev.) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Cypress Hall (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - CERAS Deck Replacement (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Landscape Projects: Vegetation Management (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Materials Research (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Parking Projects (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Path Lab Windows (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - PEDS Surge Buildings (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - RAF II Modular Siding (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Site Analysis for IIS (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Stone Building Renovation (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Tresidder, Chill Water Roof Fans (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Tresidder, Roof Fan Installation (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - World Cup Soccer (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Advanced Materials Research (AMR) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Advanced Materials Research (AMR) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Advanced Materials Research (AMR) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Advanced Materials Research (AMR) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Advanced Materials Research (AMR) (slides/pix) (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Advanced Materials Research (AMR) (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - ECH [Electronic Communication Hub]- West Campus (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - ECH - West Campus (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - ECH - West Campus (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - ECH - West Campus (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Maples Accessibility (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Maples Accessibility (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Stadium Lighting - Football (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Page Mill Sound Wall (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Maples Pavilion Renovation (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Gordon Hampton Memorial (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Lyman Graduate Housing and CD Path (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Rugby Field Study (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - GSB - Bldg. 350 Renovation (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Student Services Building (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Building 160 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Building 160 - Preliminary Seismic Formulation February 1999 (spiral bound) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Row Houses (inc. 7057, 7058) - submittal (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Row Houses (inc. 7057, 7058) - budget (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Row Houses (inc. 7057, 7058) - reviews (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Row Houses (inc. 7057, 7058) - meetings (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Row Houses (inc. 7057, 7058) - graphics (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Row Houses (inc. 7057, 7058) - graphics, continued (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - French House Renovations (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - DKE (Delta Kappa Epsilon) Renovations (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Kairos Renovations (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Abrams Midrise Seismic Update (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Escondido Village Site 3 - EV 3 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Escondido Village Site 3 - EV 3 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Hoskins (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Toyon Hall CIP Renovation (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Branner (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Ginzton Courtyard Landscape (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Chill Water Exp. Phase 1 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Gas Station (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Green Library Reconstruction oversized drawings (Box 25)
  - MC/CE Buiding 02-520/542 oversized drawings (Box 25)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2005-117
  - Stanford Sand Hill Road Corridor Projects. Volume 6. Prepared for the City of Palo Alto by EIP Associates, January 10, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Sand Hill Road Corridor Projects. Volume 7. Prepared for the City of Palo Alto by EIP Associates, January 10, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Sand Hill Road Corridor Projects. Volume 8. Prepared for the City of Palo Alto by EIP Associates, January 10, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sand Hill Road Projects 1996 [9 page color brochure] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Regional Planning of the Stanford Campus, September, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - West Campus, Jordan Quad, Searsville Region Plan, April 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stanford's Proposed Building Plans: 1988-2000 (Published by the Office of Public Affairs) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lake Lagunita Area Plan Report, December 4, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Regional Planning of the Stanford Campus, September, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2005-300
  - GLW [Green Library West]: FEMA info/Loma Prieta Repairs (1) - includes images of planks made from oak tree by the mausoleum (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - GLW: FEMA info/Loma Prieta Repairs (2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - GLW: FEMA info/Loma Prieta Repairs (3) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - GLW: FEMA info/Loma Prieta Repairs (4) - preservation concerns (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - GLW: FEMA info/Loma Prieta Repairs (5) - construction costs (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - GLW: FEMA info/Loma Prieta Repairs (6) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GLW: FEMA info/Loma Prieta Repairs (7) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Arrillaga Recreation Center - justification 2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Art Museum bronze doors and skylight sealant (includes slides and photos) 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Lane History Corner plaque 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Piggott Corner carving 1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - SEQ 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - University Facilities and the ADA 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Transition Plan to Accessiblity at Stanford, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Transition Plan for Stanford University: Making University Programs and Facilities Accessible to Physically Limited Students, Faculty, Staff, and Community Members, March 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Artices [photocopies]: D. Stazdes "The Visual Rhetoric of the Leland Stanfod Manion in Sacramento" and Tutorow " Captain Nicholas T. Smith from Schodack to San Carlos" (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2006-001
  - Draft Community Plan for Stanford University Lands in Unincorporated Santa Clara County; an explanatory document for public review and comment. September 20, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Letter, D. Neuman to Anne Draper (Santa Clara County Planning Director), with document " Stanford University Urban Unincorporated Area Issues and Policies", September 20, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Application to modify the 1989 Santa Clara County General Use Permit for Stanford University, September 20, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2006-291
  - Near West Campus Plan, Summary Planning Report, January 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Near West Campus Plan, Supplementary Planning Report, May 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Near West Campus Connective Elements Projects, September 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Foothills Region Plan, Phase I, August 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Plan for Athletics, Physical Education & Recreation (Elbasani & Logan Architects), September 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Campus Center Region Plan, May 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bonair Region Plan, April 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2006-323
  - Medical Center Signage Committee 1983-85 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Inner Campus Lights: Convert to Mercury Vapor, 1981-84 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - William Lam Resume (outdoor lighting consultant) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Willow Road Extension, Stanford Shopping Center Landscaping, 1982-84 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Student Parking- Interim and Long Range, 1982-83 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Escondido Road Barrier/Bing Parking 1982-85 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GPI Interim Parking Lots 1981-83 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Parking Lot- Panama Rd./Samuel Morris Way 1983-84 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Pathway Program 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous University Parking Info 1975-83 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Parking Utilization Info 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Space Planning Advisory Group 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Parking Structure 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Parking Info SU D.P.S. 1981-84 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Safety Committee- Bicycles, 1974-75 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Medical Center Parking Analysis 1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Traffic Agreements & Reports 1985-89 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Medical Center Design Guidelines 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - General Plant Improvement Project Ideas/Forms 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Physics Tank Plaque 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sand Hill Rd. Planning 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - West Campus/Jordan Quad/Searsville Region Plans 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Contributions by Landscape Architects to Recent SU Campus Developments 1980-83 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - West Campus Support Area (#2236) 1 of 2, 1985-88 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - West Campus Support Area (#2236) 2 of 2, 1983-85 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Overhead Photo (west campus?) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cumulative Air Quality 1988-89 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Medical Center Entryway (#2386) 1 of 3, 1984-87 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Medical Center Entryway (#2386) 2 of 3, 1987-88 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Medical Center Entryway (#2386) 3 of 3, 1987-88 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Ramps on Campus PC, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Details: Paving (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Exterior Lighting, 1979-84 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Vincent Marsh, historic preservation consultant, report on Salvatierra Walk buildings (with photos), 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous: Quad buildings, Campus Drive, and others (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Paint analysis reports: Branner Hall, 2001; Salvatierra Walk buildings, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Sand Hill Road, newspaper clippings, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Clippings on Stanford University, assorted topics (photocopied) 1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Clippings on Stanford University, assorted topics (newsprint) 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Architecture/Construction Landscape Architecture, newsprint clippings, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Local Issues/Development, clippings 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Higher Education, clippings 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Transportation, clippings 1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Economic Developments, clippings 1991 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Quality Issues, clippings 1991 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Circulation and parking reports/plans 1958-66 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Student Housing Study, 15 Feb. 1962 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Hospital / Medical Center miscellany, 1986-99 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Conservation and Use Plan for the Stanford Dish Area, ca. 2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Addressing the Housing Shortage: What Stanford University is Doing to Help, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Reagan Library area plan, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - CD-R disc " memchu.ppt CPF 10/25/02" [could not read disc 12/2009] (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - " Dream Team" [planning for Stanford/PA transit area] 1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Hospital Expansion 1983-2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1990 Lighting Plan (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Statement of Joe Simitian Regarding Stanford land Use Application Tuesday, Oct. 24, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Review of Parking Supply and Demand at Stanford 1978-79 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Parking Study A Summarization, Stanford University, circa 1964 (Box 6)
  - Preliminary Parking Master Plan (several copies) 1963 (Box 6)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2007-075
  - Fairchild Sciences Building, Sch. of Medicine: plans, memoranda, notes, photos (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - University of Michigan. Medical School Facility Master Planning Analysis, August 1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Medical SChool Office Building, Draft Report, PRC Engineering, May 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University Medical Center. Long Range Plan. Facitililties. Caudill Rowlett Scott Architects. October 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Extended Summary of the Report of the Stanford University School of Medicine Institutional Planning Committee, April 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Future Academic Programs and Resource Needs of the Clinical Departments, Stanford University School of Medicine, Institutional Planning Committee, December 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)